// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
  {
  numb: 1,
  question: "Which organization defines web standards ?",
  answer: "World Wide Web Consortium",
  options: [
    "Apple Inc.",
    "IBM Corporation",
    "World Wide Web Consortium",
    "Microsoft Corporation"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 2,
  question: "HTML is considered ?",
  answer: "Markup language",
  options: [
    "OOP language",
    "Programming language",
    "Markup language",
    "High level language"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 3,
  question: "HTML was first offered in what year ?",
  answer: "1990",
  options: [
    "1945",
    "1990",
    "2000",
    "1995"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 4,
  question: "Who is the primary HTML author?",
  answer: "Tim Berners-Lee",
  options: [
    "Brendan Eich",
    "Web developer",
    "Tim Berners-Lee",
    "Google Inc"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 5,
  question: "If we want to style only one element, which css selector will we use?",
  answer: "id",
  options: [
    "the element tag",
    "id",
    "class",
    "all of the above"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 6,
  question: "The HTML tag that specifies an embedded CSS style in an element is called ?",
  answer: "style",
  options: [
    "style",
    "link",
    "stylesheet",
    "style.css"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 7,
  question: "An HTML document can contain ?",
  answer: "all of the above",
  options: [
    "attributes",
    "tags",
    "plain text",
    "all of the above"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 8,
  question: "If we want to wrap text around an image, which CSS property are we going to use?",
  answer: "float",
  options: [
    "justify-content",
    "align",
    "float",
    "all of the above"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 9,
  question: "what are the ordered elements of a commit",
  answer: "add-commit-pull-push",
  options: [
    "add-commit-push",
    "add-commit-pull-push",
    "Add-Commit-Pull-Push",
    "the last two answers"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 10,
  question: "the machine representation of 13 is ?",
  answer: "1101",
  options: [
    "1001",
    "1101",
    "1100",
    "none of the above"
  ]
},

];